[
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Which category best describes React?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Security standard",
      "Styling language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains React?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "In which year was React first released?",
    "options": [
      "1997",
      "1999",
      "1998",
      "2000"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with React?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      NaN,
      ".js",
      ".yaml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of React?",
    "options": [
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize React?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install react"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install react"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with React?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "JavaScript",
      "Python",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of React?",
    "options": [
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Event loop",
      "Routing",
      "Schema‑based queries"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Component‑based UI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to React?",
    "options": [
      "GCP",
      "SQLite",
      "Vue",
      "Bash"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Vue"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React",
    "question": "Under which license is React primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Which category best describes Python?",
    "options": [
      "Technology",
      "Testing framework",
      "Architecture style",
      "Data library"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Python?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "In which year was Python first released?",
    "options": [
      "2020",
      "2019",
      "2018",
      "2021"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2018"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Python?",
    "options": [
      ".rs",
      NaN,
      ".css",
      ".py"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".py"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Python?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with technology",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Python?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Python?",
    "options": [
      "TypeScript",
      "Python",
      "C++",
      "C#"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Python?",
    "options": [
      "Event loop",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Model training",
      "Feature X"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Python?",
    "options": [
      "GraphQL",
      "Scikit-Learn",
      "TypeScript",
      "Mocha"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scikit-Learn"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Python",
    "question": "Under which license is Python primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "BSD",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Which category best describes Java?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Technology",
      "Markup language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Java?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Community",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "In which year was Java first released?",
    "options": [
      "2004",
      "2003",
      "2005",
      "2001"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2003"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Java?",
    "options": [
      ".java",
      ".css",
      ".js",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".java"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Java?",
    "options": [
      "Working with technology",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Java?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Java?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      "C++",
      "Java",
      "Kotlin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Java?",
    "options": [
      "Scalable compute",
      "Token grant types",
      "Native bridges",
      "Feature X"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Java?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "AWS",
      "Flutter",
      "RabbitMQ"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "RabbitMQ"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Java",
    "question": "Under which license is Java primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "BSD",
      "Proprietary",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which category best describes JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Operating system",
      "Technology",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Security protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "In which year was JavaScript first released?",
    "options": [
      "1992",
      "1990",
      "1987",
      "1988"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1990"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      ".css",
      ".py",
      ".js",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".js"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Working with technology",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Kotlin",
      "JavaScript",
      "Swift",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Event loop",
      "Feature X",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Native bridges"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "Kubernetes",
      "Jest",
      "Kotlin",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kubernetes"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Under which license is JavaScript primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Which category best describes C++?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Security standard",
      "Technology",
      "Cloud platform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains C++?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Community",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "In which year was C++ first released?",
    "options": [
      "2007",
      "2005",
      "2003",
      "2002"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2005"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with C++?",
    "options": [
      ".yaml",
      NaN,
      ".cpp",
      ".cs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".cpp"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of C++?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize C++?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with C++?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "C++",
      "Python",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C++"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of C++?",
    "options": [
      "Event loop",
      "Full‑duplex",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Feature X"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to C++?",
    "options": [
      "Django",
      "Git",
      "TypeScript",
      "Next.js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "TypeScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C++",
    "question": "Under which license is C++ primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Which category best describes C#?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Technology",
      "Networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains C#?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "In which year was C# first released?",
    "options": [
      "2010",
      "2012",
      "2011",
      "2007"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2010"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with C#?",
    "options": [
      ".py",
      ".yaml",
      ".cs",
      ".js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".cs"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of C#?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize C#?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with C#?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "Python",
      "Swift"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C#"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of C#?",
    "options": [
      "Model training",
      "Feature X",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Automation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to C#?",
    "options": [
      "GCP",
      "Angular",
      "AWS",
      "Java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "skill": "C#",
    "question": "Under which license is C# primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Which category best describes Go?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Security standard",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Go?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "In which year was Go first released?",
    "options": [
      "2009",
      "2011",
      "2008",
      "2006"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2009"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Go?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      ".go",
      ".cs",
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".go"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Go?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Go?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Go?",
    "options": [
      "Kotlin",
      "Java",
      "Go",
      "Rust"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Go"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Go?",
    "options": [
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Data storage",
      "Feature X"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Go?",
    "options": [
      "PyTorch",
      "JWT",
      "TypeScript",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JWT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Go",
    "question": "Under which license is Go primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Which category best describes Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Security standard",
      "Database",
      "Technology",
      "Styling language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "In which year was Rust first released?",
    "options": [
      "2019",
      "2016",
      "2020",
      "2018"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2019"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Rust?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      ".java",
      ".cs",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".rs"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with technology",
      "Working with back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Rust?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "Python",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Rust"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Feature X",
      "Event loop",
      "Native bridges",
      "Cascade"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Rust?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "FastAPI",
      "Vue",
      "Next.js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Go"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Rust",
    "question": "Under which license is Rust primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Which category best describes Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Technology",
      "Testing framework",
      "Markup language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "In which year was Swift first released?",
    "options": [
      "2014",
      "2015",
      "2013",
      "2016"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2016"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Swift?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      ".html",
      ".swift",
      ".yaml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".swift"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Swift?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "Kotlin",
      "Java",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Swift"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Scalable compute",
      "Feature X",
      "Strong typing",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Swift?",
    "options": [
      "Kafka",
      "Microservices",
      "Jenkins",
      "CSS"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Microservices"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Swift",
    "question": "Under which license is Swift primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Which category best describes Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Markup language",
      "Technology",
      "Messaging system"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "In which year was Kotlin first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2008",
      "2007",
      "2006"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      ".json",
      ".kt",
      ".yaml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".kt"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "Working with technology",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "Python",
      "JavaScript",
      "Kotlin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kotlin"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "Signed tokens",
      "Assertions",
      "Feature X",
      "Publish‑subscribe"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Feature X"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Kotlin?",
    "options": [
      "Bash",
      "GraphQL",
      "Docker",
      "Cypress"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Bash"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kotlin",
    "question": "Under which license is Kotlin primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Which category best describes Angular?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Database",
      "Mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Angular?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "In which year was Angular first released?",
    "options": [
      "2006",
      "2003",
      "2007",
      "2005"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2006"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Angular?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".java",
      ".css",
      ".js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Angular?",
    "options": [
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Angular?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "npm install @angular/cli"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install @angular/cli"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Angular?",
    "options": [
      "C++",
      NaN,
      "C#",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Angular?",
    "options": [
      "Data manipulation",
      "Cascade",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Component‑based UI"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Component‑based UI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Angular?",
    "options": [
      "Terraform",
      "GitHub Actions",
      "GCP",
      "Vue"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Terraform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Angular",
    "question": "Under which license is Angular primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Which category best describes Vue?",
    "options": [
      "Cloud platform",
      "DevOps tool",
      "Data library",
      "Front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Vue?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Community",
      "Independent",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "In which year was Vue first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2014",
      "2013",
      "2010"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2011"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Vue?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      ".cs",
      NaN,
      ".css"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Vue?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Vue?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      NaN,
      "npm install vue",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install vue"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Vue?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      "JavaScript",
      "TypeScript",
      "Swift"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Vue?",
    "options": [
      "Data manipulation",
      "Full‑duplex",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Command scripting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Component‑based UI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Vue?",
    "options": [
      "MySQL",
      "GitHub Actions",
      "RabbitMQ",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Actions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Vue",
    "question": "Under which license is Vue primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Which category best describes Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Architecture style",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "API technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "In which year was Svelte first released?",
    "options": [
      "1995",
      "1997",
      "1994",
      "1992"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Svelte?",
    "options": [
      ".py",
      ".json",
      NaN,
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "npm install svelte",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install svelte"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "Python",
      "Swift",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Semantic tags",
      "Automation",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Command scripting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Component‑based UI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Svelte?",
    "options": [
      "Flask",
      "PostgreSQL",
      "Jest",
      "Pandas"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "PostgreSQL"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Svelte",
    "question": "Under which license is Svelte primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Which category best describes Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Mobile framework",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Cloud platform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "In which year was Next.js first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2008",
      "2010",
      "2009"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Next.js?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".ts",
      ".cs",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with front‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "npx create-next-app",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npx create-next-app"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Python",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Loose coupling",
      "Model training",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Full‑duplex"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Component‑based UI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Next.js?",
    "options": [
      "Scikit-Learn",
      "WebSockets",
      "MongoDB",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scikit-Learn"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Next.js",
    "question": "Under which license is Next.js primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Which category best describes Express?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Mobile framework",
      "Networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Express?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Community",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "In which year was Express first released?",
    "options": [
      "2003",
      "2000",
      "2002",
      "1999"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2002"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Express?",
    "options": [
      ".go",
      NaN,
      ".sql",
      ".html"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Express?",
    "options": [
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Express?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "npm install express",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install express"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Express?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "Go",
      "Rust",
      "C++"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Express?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Data manipulation",
      "Data storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Express?",
    "options": [
      "MySQL",
      "Jest",
      "Redis",
      "GitHub Actions"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MySQL"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Express",
    "question": "Under which license is Express primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "Public Domain",
      "BSD",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Which category best describes NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Messaging system",
      "API technology",
      "Testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "In which year was NestJS first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2008",
      "2014",
      "2013"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2011"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with NestJS?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      NaN,
      ".yaml",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install @nestjs/cli"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install @nestjs/cli"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "JavaScript",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Routing",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to NestJS?",
    "options": [
      "Azure",
      "Java",
      "GCP",
      "Rust"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NestJS",
    "question": "Under which license is NestJS primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "BSD",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Which category best describes Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "In which year was Spring first released?",
    "options": [
      "1993",
      "1996",
      "1994",
      "1997"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Spring?",
    "options": [
      ".ts",
      ".go",
      NaN,
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with devops tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Spring?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Model training",
      "Kernel",
      "Command scripting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Spring?",
    "options": [
      "Linux",
      "Swift",
      "React",
      "Jest"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Swift"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Spring",
    "question": "Under which license is Spring primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Which category best describes Django?",
    "options": [
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Markup language",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Security protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Django?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "In which year was Django first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2005",
      "2009",
      "2008"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Django?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".css",
      ".sql",
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Django?",
    "options": [
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Django?",
    "options": [
      "pip install django",
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install django"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Django?",
    "options": [
      "JavaScript",
      "Rust",
      NaN,
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Django?",
    "options": [
      "Cascade",
      "Event loop",
      "Model training",
      "Routing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Django?",
    "options": [
      "FastAPI",
      "C#",
      "Microservices",
      "Linux"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C#"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Django",
    "question": "Under which license is Django primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "MIT",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Which category best describes Flask?",
    "options": [
      "Markup language",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Messaging system",
      "Front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Flask?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "In which year was Flask first released?",
    "options": [
      "2011",
      "2005",
      "2007",
      "2008"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Flask?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      NaN,
      ".go",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Flask?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Flask?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install flask",
      NaN,
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install flask"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Flask?",
    "options": [
      "C++",
      "Java",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Flask?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Cascade",
      "Native bridges",
      "Command scripting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Flask?",
    "options": [
      "Svelte",
      "Cypress",
      "HTML",
      "Git"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Cypress"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flask",
    "question": "Under which license is Flask primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Which category best describes FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Testing framework",
      "Security standard",
      "DevOps tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "In which year was FastAPI first released?",
    "options": [
      "2012",
      "2013",
      "2015",
      "2010"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2013"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      ".yaml",
      ".cs",
      ".go",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with back‑end framework",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install fastapi"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install fastapi"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "Go",
      "Kotlin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Semantic tags",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Routing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to FastAPI?",
    "options": [
      "Terraform",
      "PostgreSQL",
      "Swift",
      "CircleCI"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Terraform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "FastAPI",
    "question": "Under which license is FastAPI primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Which category best describes TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Cloud platform",
      "Mobile framework",
      "Machine learning library",
      "Back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "In which year was TensorFlow first released?",
    "options": [
      "2009",
      "2015",
      "2014",
      "2012"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2012"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      ".css",
      ".json",
      ".java",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Working with machine learning library",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "pip install tensorflow",
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install tensorflow"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      NaN,
      "Python",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Loose coupling",
      "Model training",
      "Command scripting",
      "Semantic tags"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Model training"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to TensorFlow?",
    "options": [
      "Git",
      "PostgreSQL",
      "PyTorch",
      "Terraform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Git"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TensorFlow",
    "question": "Under which license is TensorFlow primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "Public Domain",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Which category best describes PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "Security protocol",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "API technology",
      "Machine learning library"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Community",
      "Independent",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "In which year was PyTorch first released?",
    "options": [
      "1987",
      "1990",
      "1993",
      "1992"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1990"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      ".cs",
      ".py",
      ".java",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "Working with machine learning library",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "pip install torch",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install torch"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "JavaScript",
      "JavaScript",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "Automation",
      "Full‑duplex",
      "Command scripting",
      "Model training"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Model training"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to PyTorch?",
    "options": [
      "JavaScript",
      "JWT",
      "Java",
      "Git"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JWT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PyTorch",
    "question": "Under which license is PyTorch primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Which category best describes Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Database",
      "Mobile framework",
      "Operating system"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "In which year was Scikit-Learn first released?",
    "options": [
      "2000",
      "1998",
      "2002",
      "2003"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2000"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".ts",
      ".js",
      ".yaml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with machine learning library"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with machine learning library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install scikit-learn",
      "npm install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install scikit-learn"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "Swift",
      "Python",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "Model training",
      "Token grant types",
      "Assertions",
      "Loose coupling"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Model training"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Scikit-Learn?",
    "options": [
      "Java",
      "NestJS",
      "RabbitMQ",
      "Jenkins"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "RabbitMQ"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Scikit-Learn",
    "question": "Under which license is Scikit-Learn primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "BSD",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Which category best describes NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "Cloud platform",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Data library",
      "Markup language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "In which year was NumPy first released?",
    "options": [
      "2014",
      "2013",
      "2016",
      "2015"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2014"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with NumPy?",
    "options": [
      ".js",
      ".ts",
      ".go",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "Working with data library",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with data library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install numpy"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install numpy"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "Kotlin",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN,
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Full‑duplex",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Data manipulation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data manipulation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to NumPy?",
    "options": [
      "FastAPI",
      "MySQL",
      "Selenium",
      "Express"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Selenium"
  },
  {
    "skill": "NumPy",
    "question": "Under which license is NumPy primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "BSD",
      "Public Domain",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Which category best describes Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Architecture style",
      "Data library",
      "Operating system"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Corporate",
      "Community",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "In which year was Pandas first released?",
    "options": [
      "2014",
      "2016",
      "2012",
      "2011"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2014"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Pandas?",
    "options": [
      ".js",
      ".html",
      ".sql",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with data library",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with data library"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install pandas",
      "npm install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install pandas"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "TypeScript",
      NaN,
      "Python",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Data manipulation",
      "Cascade",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data manipulation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Pandas?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "GCP",
      "Ansible",
      "Vue"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GCP"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Pandas",
    "question": "Under which license is Pandas primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "BSD",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Which category best describes MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Database",
      "Security protocol",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Styling language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "In which year was MySQL first released?",
    "options": [
      "2006",
      "2007",
      "2004",
      "2005"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2007"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with MySQL?",
    "options": [
      ".rs",
      ".html",
      ".sql",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sql"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize MySQL?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "TypeScript",
      "Python",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Loose coupling",
      "Data manipulation",
      "Data storage",
      "Native bridges"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data storage"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to MySQL?",
    "options": [
      "Pandas",
      "NumPy",
      "CircleCI",
      "Java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "CircleCI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MySQL",
    "question": "Under which license is MySQL primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "MIT",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Which category best describes PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Networking protocol",
      "Database",
      "Data library",
      "Shell"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "In which year was PostgreSQL first released?",
    "options": [
      "2006",
      "2007",
      "2005",
      "2004"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2007"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      ".js",
      ".cs",
      ".sql",
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sql"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Java",
      "TypeScript",
      NaN,
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Event loop",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Data storage",
      "Routing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data storage"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to PostgreSQL?",
    "options": [
      "Spring",
      "MongoDB",
      "WebSockets",
      "Rust"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "WebSockets"
  },
  {
    "skill": "PostgreSQL",
    "question": "Under which license is PostgreSQL primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Which category best describes MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "Operating system",
      "Database",
      "Machine learning library",
      "Programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "In which year was MongoDB first released?",
    "options": [
      "1992",
      "1989",
      "1995",
      "1994"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      ".go",
      ".sql",
      ".ts"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sql"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN,
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "Semantic tags",
      "Model training",
      "Routing",
      "Data storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data storage"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to MongoDB?",
    "options": [
      "NumPy",
      "C++",
      "Rust",
      "Kotlin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kotlin"
  },
  {
    "skill": "MongoDB",
    "question": "Under which license is MongoDB primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Which category best describes Redis?",
    "options": [
      "Database",
      "Machine learning library",
      "API technology",
      "Markup language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Redis?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Community",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "In which year was Redis first released?",
    "options": [
      "1998",
      "1995",
      "1996",
      "1993"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1995"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Redis?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      ".rs",
      ".js",
      ".py"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sql"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Redis?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Redis?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Redis?",
    "options": [
      "Java",
      "Rust",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Redis?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Data storage",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Strong typing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data storage"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Redis?",
    "options": [
      "GitHub Actions",
      "Cypress",
      "FastAPI",
      "TensorFlow"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "TensorFlow"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Redis",
    "question": "Under which license is Redis primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Which category best describes SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "Machine learning library",
      "Operating system",
      "Database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "In which year was SQLite first released?",
    "options": [
      "2003",
      "1999",
      "2001",
      "2000"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2001"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with SQLite?",
    "options": [
      ".cs",
      ".sql",
      ".rs",
      ".go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sql"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with database"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize SQLite?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "Kotlin",
      "Java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "Model training",
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Data storage",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Data storage"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to SQLite?",
    "options": [
      "Linux",
      "React",
      "PyTorch",
      "Flutter"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Flutter"
  },
  {
    "skill": "SQLite",
    "question": "Under which license is SQLite primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Which category best describes Docker?",
    "options": [
      "Mobile framework",
      "Testing framework",
      "DevOps tool",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Docker?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "In which year was Docker first released?",
    "options": [
      "2014",
      "2013",
      "2011",
      "2017"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2014"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Docker?",
    "options": [
      ".yml",
      ".js",
      ".rs",
      ".go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Docker?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with devops tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Docker?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install docker.io",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "apt-get install docker.io"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Docker?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "JavaScript",
      "Rust",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Docker?",
    "options": [
      "Kernel",
      "Automation",
      "Strong typing",
      "Schema‑based queries"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Docker?",
    "options": [
      "NestJS",
      "CSS",
      "Kafka",
      "FastAPI"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kafka"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Docker",
    "question": "Under which license is Docker primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Which category best describes Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Shell",
      "Messaging system",
      "DevOps tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Corporate",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "In which year was Kubernetes first released?",
    "options": [
      "2008",
      "2011",
      "2014",
      "2010"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2011"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      ".html",
      NaN,
      ".js",
      ".yml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with devops tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "kubectl apply -f",
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "kubectl apply -f"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "TypeScript",
      NaN,
      "Kotlin",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "Automation",
      "Strong typing",
      "Native bridges",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Kubernetes?",
    "options": [
      "FastAPI",
      "MongoDB",
      "Azure",
      "MySQL"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "FastAPI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kubernetes",
    "question": "Under which license is Kubernetes primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Which category best describes Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "In which year was Terraform first released?",
    "options": [
      "2016",
      "2019",
      "2017",
      "2014"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2016"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Terraform?",
    "options": [
      ".ts",
      ".js",
      ".yml",
      ".cs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with devops tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      NaN,
      "brew install terraform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "brew install terraform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "Python",
      "TypeScript",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "Strong typing",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Automation",
      "Component‑based UI"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Terraform?",
    "options": [
      "Flask",
      "Pandas",
      "WebSockets",
      "GraphQL"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Pandas"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Terraform",
    "question": "Under which license is Terraform primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Which category best describes Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Operating system",
      "Machine learning library"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "In which year was Ansible first released?",
    "options": [
      "2020",
      "2022",
      "2018",
      "2023"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2020"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Ansible?",
    "options": [
      ".yml",
      ".go",
      ".rs",
      ".css"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "pip install ansible",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": "pip install ansible"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      NaN,
      "Rust",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "Semantic tags",
      "Model training",
      "Automation",
      "Native bridges"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Ansible?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "GCP",
      "MongoDB",
      "PyTorch"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "PyTorch"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Ansible",
    "question": "Under which license is Ansible primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Which category best describes Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "API technology",
      "DevOps tool",
      "Shell",
      "Networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "In which year was Jenkins first released?",
    "options": [
      "2005",
      "2006",
      "2007",
      "2003"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2005"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".json",
      ".sql",
      ".yml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install jenkins",
      "brew install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "apt-get install jenkins"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "Kotlin",
      "Go",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Automation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Jenkins?",
    "options": [
      "Angular",
      "Scikit-Learn",
      "PyTorch",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Go"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jenkins",
    "question": "Under which license is Jenkins primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Which category best describes GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Styling language",
      "Operating system",
      "DevOps tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "In which year was GitHub Actions first released?",
    "options": [
      "2015",
      "2012",
      "2014",
      "2013"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2012"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      ".js",
      NaN,
      ".yml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "TypeScript",
      "C#",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "Loose coupling",
      "Automation",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Data storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to GitHub Actions?",
    "options": [
      "GCP",
      "NumPy",
      "PyTorch",
      "Svelte"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "PyTorch"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GitHub Actions",
    "question": "Under which license is GitHub Actions primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Which category best describes CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Cloud platform",
      "Front‑end framework",
      "Mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "In which year was CircleCI first released?",
    "options": [
      "2018",
      "2021",
      "2020",
      "2017"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2018"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      ".go",
      ".yml",
      ".css",
      ".html"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "Kotlin",
      "Swift",
      "TypeScript",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "Token grant types",
      "Event loop",
      "Semantic tags",
      "Automation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to CircleCI?",
    "options": [
      "RabbitMQ",
      "Flask",
      "Cypress",
      "Scikit-Learn"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scikit-Learn"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CircleCI",
    "question": "Under which license is CircleCI primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Which category best describes AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Security standard",
      "Cloud platform",
      "Architecture style"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Community",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "In which year was AWS first released?",
    "options": [
      "1995",
      "1998",
      "1997",
      "1996"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1996"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with AWS?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".css",
      ".sql",
      ".cs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with cloud platform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize AWS?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "aws configure",
      NaN,
      "pip install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "aws configure"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "Kotlin",
      "Java",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Cascade",
      "Token grant types",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Strong typing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scalable compute"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to AWS?",
    "options": [
      "RabbitMQ",
      "Python",
      "GraphQL",
      "GitHub Actions"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Actions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "AWS",
    "question": "Under which license is AWS primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Which category best describes Azure?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Cloud platform",
      "Operating system",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Azure?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "In which year was Azure first released?",
    "options": [
      "2001",
      "1999",
      "2002",
      "2005"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2002"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Azure?",
    "options": [
      ".css",
      ".html",
      ".yaml",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Azure?",
    "options": [
      "Working with cloud platform",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with devops tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Azure?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "az login",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "az login"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Azure?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "Swift",
      "JavaScript",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Azure?",
    "options": [
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Event loop",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Routing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scalable compute"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Azure?",
    "options": [
      "Jest",
      "C++",
      "TensorFlow",
      "Express"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Express"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Azure",
    "question": "Under which license is Azure primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Which category best describes GCP?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Shell",
      "Machine learning library",
      "Cloud platform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains GCP?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "In which year was GCP first released?",
    "options": [
      "2004",
      "2006",
      "2002",
      "2003"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2004"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with GCP?",
    "options": [
      ".cs",
      ".html",
      ".java",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of GCP?",
    "options": [
      "Working with cloud platform",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with cloud platform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize GCP?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "gcloud init",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "gcloud init"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with GCP?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN,
      "TypeScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of GCP?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Full‑duplex"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Scalable compute"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to GCP?",
    "options": [
      "MySQL",
      "Kafka",
      "AWS",
      "TensorFlow"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "TensorFlow"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GCP",
    "question": "Under which license is GCP primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "BSD",
      "MIT",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Which category best describes Linux?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Operating system",
      "API technology",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Operating system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Linux?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Community",
      "Foundation",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Community"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "In which year was Linux first released?",
    "options": [
      "1997",
      "2000",
      "1999",
      "1998"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1999"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Linux?",
    "options": [
      ".yaml",
      ".cs",
      NaN,
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Linux?",
    "options": [
      "Working with operating system",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with operating system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Linux?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Linux?",
    "options": [
      "Swift",
      "Go",
      "Python",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Linux?",
    "options": [
      "Data manipulation",
      "Native bridges",
      "Cascade",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kernel"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Linux?",
    "options": [
      "GraphQL",
      "NestJS",
      "RabbitMQ",
      "MySQL"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GraphQL"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Linux",
    "question": "Under which license is Linux primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Which category best describes Git?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Machine learning library",
      "Security standard",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "DevOps tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Git?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "In which year was Git first released?",
    "options": [
      "2006",
      "2004",
      "2005",
      "2007"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2004"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Git?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".ts",
      ".rs",
      ".yml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".yml"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Git?",
    "options": [
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with devops tool"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Git?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Git?",
    "options": [
      "JavaScript",
      NaN,
      "Go",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Git?",
    "options": [
      "Semantic tags",
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Automation",
      "Cascade"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Automation"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Git?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      "Bash",
      "React",
      "Kubernetes"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C#"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Git",
    "question": "Under which license is Git primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "MIT",
      "BSD",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Which category best describes Bash?",
    "options": [
      "Data library",
      "API technology",
      "Shell",
      "Back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Shell"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Bash?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "In which year was Bash first released?",
    "options": [
      "1998",
      "2000",
      "2003",
      "1999"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2000"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Bash?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".html",
      ".go",
      ".sh"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".sh"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Bash?",
    "options": [
      "Working with shell",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with shell"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Bash?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Bash?",
    "options": [
      "JavaScript",
      "C++",
      "Rust",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Bash?",
    "options": [
      "Scalable compute",
      "Semantic tags",
      "Cascade",
      "Command scripting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Command scripting"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Bash?",
    "options": [
      "Node.js",
      "Docker",
      "Ansible",
      "Kubernetes"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Ansible"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Bash",
    "question": "Under which license is Bash primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Proprietary"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Which category best describes HTML?",
    "options": [
      "Database",
      "Markup language",
      "Mobile framework",
      "Security protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Markup language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains HTML?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "In which year was HTML first released?",
    "options": [
      "1999",
      "2001",
      "1998",
      "1996"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1999"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with HTML?",
    "options": [
      ".java",
      ".html",
      NaN,
      ".yaml"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".html"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of HTML?",
    "options": [
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with markup language",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with markup language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize HTML?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with HTML?",
    "options": [
      "JavaScript",
      "Rust",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of HTML?",
    "options": [
      "Kernel",
      "Semantic tags",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Data manipulation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Semantic tags"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to HTML?",
    "options": [
      "PostgreSQL",
      "NumPy",
      "GitHub Actions",
      "Flask"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Actions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "HTML",
    "question": "Under which license is HTML primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "MIT",
      "BSD",
      "Public Domain"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Which category best describes CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Security standard",
      "Styling language",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Architecture style"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Styling language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Community",
      "Corporate",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "In which year was CSS first released?",
    "options": [
      "1994",
      "1992",
      "1991",
      "1989"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with CSS?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".java",
      ".js",
      ".css"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".css"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with styling language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize CSS?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Go",
      "Java",
      "JavaScript",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Data storage",
      "Strong typing",
      "Token grant types",
      "Cascade"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Cascade"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to CSS?",
    "options": [
      "Spring",
      "C#",
      "TypeScript",
      "Ansible"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Ansible"
  },
  {
    "skill": "CSS",
    "question": "Under which license is CSS primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Which category best describes TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "Machine learning library",
      "Markup language",
      "Programming language",
      "Mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Programming language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "In which year was TypeScript first released?",
    "options": [
      "1994",
      "1995",
      "1992",
      "1996"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      ".ts",
      ".yaml",
      ".java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": ".ts"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with programming language"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      NaN,
      "npm install typescript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "npm install typescript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN,
      "TypeScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "TypeScript"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "Automation",
      "Semantic tags",
      "Model training",
      "Strong typing"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Strong typing"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to TypeScript?",
    "options": [
      "Linux",
      "Spring",
      "FastAPI",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "FastAPI"
  },
  {
    "skill": "TypeScript",
    "question": "Under which license is TypeScript primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Apache‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Which category best describes Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "DevOps tool",
      "Back‑end framework",
      "Mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Back‑end runtime"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Community",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "In which year was Node.js first released?",
    "options": [
      "2008",
      "2014",
      "2010",
      "2011"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2011"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Node.js?",
    "options": [
      ".json",
      NaN,
      ".cs",
      ".js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with styling language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with back‑end runtime"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "Python",
      NaN,
      "Kotlin",
      "C#"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "Event loop",
      "Scalable compute",
      "Kernel",
      "Data storage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Event loop"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Node.js?",
    "options": [
      "C++",
      "Svelte",
      "AWS",
      "PostgreSQL"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "AWS"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Node.js",
    "question": "Under which license is Node.js primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "BSD",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Which category best describes GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "Architecture style",
      "Styling language",
      "API technology",
      "Front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "API technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "In which year was GraphQL first released?",
    "options": [
      "1999",
      "1996",
      "1997",
      "2001"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1999"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      ".go",
      ".java",
      ".html",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with front‑end framework",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with api technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with api technology"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "TypeScript",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Native bridges",
      "Command scripting",
      "Assertions"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Schema‑based queries"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to GraphQL?",
    "options": [
      "TensorFlow",
      "Angular",
      "Node.js",
      "Selenium"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Node.js"
  },
  {
    "skill": "GraphQL",
    "question": "Under which license is GraphQL primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Which category best describes Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "Operating system",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Messaging system",
      "Cloud platform"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Messaging system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Corporate",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "In which year was Kafka first released?",
    "options": [
      "2015",
      "2017",
      "2018",
      "2019"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2018"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Kafka?",
    "options": [
      ".js",
      ".html",
      NaN,
      ".go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with messaging system"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with messaging system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "C++",
      "Rust",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "Semantic tags",
      "Publish‑subscribe",
      "Strong typing",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Publish‑subscribe"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Kafka?",
    "options": [
      "MongoDB",
      "TypeScript",
      "JavaScript",
      "Swift"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Swift"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Kafka",
    "question": "Under which license is Kafka primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Which category best describes RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "Messaging system",
      "Security standard",
      "Styling language",
      "Programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Messaging system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "In which year was RabbitMQ first released?",
    "options": [
      "1994",
      "1992",
      "1993",
      "1990"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".js",
      ".cs",
      ".html"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with messaging system"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "pip install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "Java",
      "Kotlin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "Automation",
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Command scripting",
      "Publish‑subscribe"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Publish‑subscribe"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to RabbitMQ?",
    "options": [
      "C++",
      "Docker",
      "Rust",
      "Bash"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Rust"
  },
  {
    "skill": "RabbitMQ",
    "question": "Under which license is RabbitMQ primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Which category best describes Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "Data library",
      "Testing framework",
      "Programming language",
      "DevOps tool"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "In which year was Selenium first released?",
    "options": [
      "2005",
      "2007",
      "2006",
      "2008"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Selenium?",
    "options": [
      ".css",
      NaN,
      ".js",
      ".ts"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      NaN,
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "TypeScript",
      "Python",
      "C++",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "Kernel",
      "Assertions",
      "Strong typing",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Assertions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Selenium?",
    "options": [
      "Vue",
      "GraphQL",
      "Go",
      "NumPy"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GraphQL"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Selenium",
    "question": "Under which license is Selenium primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Proprietary",
      "Public Domain"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Which category best describes Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "Security standard",
      "Markup language",
      "Security protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Independent",
      "Various",
      "Foundation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "In which year was Cypress first released?",
    "options": [
      "1992",
      "1990",
      "1993",
      "1995"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1993"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Cypress?",
    "options": [
      ".py",
      ".html",
      ".json",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with security standard"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "brew install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Python",
      "Kotlin",
      "Rust",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Assertions",
      "Loose coupling",
      "Model training",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Assertions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Cypress?",
    "options": [
      "Selenium",
      "Flutter",
      "Terraform",
      "Next.js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Flutter"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Cypress",
    "question": "Under which license is Cypress primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "BSD",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "GPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Which category best describes Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "API technology",
      "Data library",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "In which year was Jest first released?",
    "options": [
      "2001",
      "1999",
      "2002",
      "2000"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1999"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Jest?",
    "options": [
      ".sql",
      NaN,
      ".java",
      ".go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with devops tool",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Jest?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "JavaScript",
      "C++",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Signed tokens",
      "Assertions",
      "Data manipulation",
      "Token grant types"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Assertions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Jest?",
    "options": [
      "Next.js",
      "Rust",
      "Flutter",
      "Pandas"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Flutter"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Jest",
    "question": "Under which license is Jest primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD",
      "MIT",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MPL‑2.0"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Which category best describes Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Database",
      "Front‑end framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "In which year was Mocha first released?",
    "options": [
      "2005",
      "2006",
      "2010",
      "2007"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2007"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Mocha?",
    "options": [
      ".yaml",
      ".py",
      NaN,
      ".cs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime",
      "Working with database",
      "Working with testing framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with testing framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      "Java",
      NaN,
      "TypeScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Event loop",
      "Assertions",
      "Publish‑subscribe"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Assertions"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Mocha?",
    "options": [
      "Scikit-Learn",
      "PostgreSQL",
      "Bash",
      "Next.js"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "PostgreSQL"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Mocha",
    "question": "Under which license is Mocha primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Which category best describes OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "DevOps tool",
      "Security protocol",
      "Security standard",
      "Programming language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Security protocol"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "Foundation",
      "Community",
      "Various",
      "Corporate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "In which year was OAuth2 first released?",
    "options": [
      "1992",
      "1990",
      "1991",
      "1989"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1992"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      ".rs",
      ".java",
      ".json",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with security protocol",
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with database"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with security protocol"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "TypeScript",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "Schema‑based queries",
      "Token grant types",
      "Data storage",
      "Semantic tags"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Token grant types"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to OAuth2?",
    "options": [
      "PyTorch",
      "TensorFlow",
      "CircleCI",
      "Mocha"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Mocha"
  },
  {
    "skill": "OAuth2",
    "question": "Under which license is OAuth2 primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "BSD",
      "Public Domain"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Which category best describes JWT?",
    "options": [
      "Security standard",
      "Markup language",
      "API technology",
      "Machine learning library"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Security standard"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains JWT?",
    "options": [
      "Corporate",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "In which year was JWT first released?",
    "options": [
      "2013",
      "2012",
      "2014",
      "2016"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2013"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with JWT?",
    "options": [
      ".rs",
      ".html",
      ".java",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of JWT?",
    "options": [
      "Working with database",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with messaging system"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with security standard"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize JWT?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "pip install package",
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with JWT?",
    "options": [
      "Python",
      "JavaScript",
      "C++",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of JWT?",
    "options": [
      "Scalable compute",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Native bridges",
      "Kernel"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Signed tokens"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to JWT?",
    "options": [
      "CircleCI",
      "Flutter",
      "GitHub Actions",
      "Java"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "skill": "JWT",
    "question": "Under which license is JWT primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "BSD"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Which category best describes WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Testing framework",
      "Networking protocol",
      "Data library",
      "Architecture style"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Networking protocol"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "In which year was WebSockets first released?",
    "options": [
      "1996",
      "1994",
      "1995",
      "1997"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      ".html",
      NaN,
      ".yaml",
      ".py"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with networking protocol"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Python",
      NaN,
      "Go",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Loose coupling",
      "Event loop",
      "Signed tokens",
      "Full‑duplex"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Full‑duplex"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to WebSockets?",
    "options": [
      "Linux",
      "Kafka",
      "Docker",
      "Flask"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Docker"
  },
  {
    "skill": "WebSockets",
    "question": "Under which license is WebSockets primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "BSD",
      "Proprietary",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "BSD"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Which category best describes Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "Architecture style",
      "Styling language",
      "Back‑end runtime",
      "Markup language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Architecture style"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "Independent",
      "Foundation",
      "Various",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Community"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "In which year was Microservices first released?",
    "options": [
      "1991",
      "1994",
      "1993",
      "1995"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1993"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Microservices?",
    "options": [
      ".java",
      NaN,
      ".cs",
      ".sql"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "Working with architecture style",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with testing framework",
      "Working with styling language"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with architecture style"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "brew install pkg",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "npm install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Microservices?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      "Rust",
      "JavaScript",
      "Go"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "Routing",
      "Data storage",
      "Token grant types",
      "Loose coupling"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Loose coupling"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Microservices?",
    "options": [
      "TensorFlow",
      "HTML",
      "Svelte",
      "JWT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "JWT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Microservices",
    "question": "Under which license is Microservices primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Public Domain",
      "MIT",
      "Proprietary",
      "Apache‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "MIT"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Which category best describes React Native?",
    "options": [
      "Database",
      "Architecture style",
      "Technology",
      "Mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Mobile framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains React Native?",
    "options": [
      "Community",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent",
      "Various"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "In which year was React Native first released?",
    "options": [
      "1993",
      "1994",
      "1995",
      "1997"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with React Native?",
    "options": [
      NaN,
      ".py",
      ".go",
      ".rs"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of React Native?",
    "options": [
      "Working with programming language",
      "Working with networking protocol",
      "Working with security standard",
      "Working with mobile framework"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with mobile framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize React Native?",
    "options": [
      "npm install package",
      "apt-get install pkg",
      "pip install package",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with React Native?",
    "options": [
      "C#",
      NaN,
      "Python",
      "Python"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of React Native?",
    "options": [
      "Native bridges",
      "Data manipulation",
      "Component‑based UI",
      "Signed tokens"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Native bridges"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to React Native?",
    "options": [
      "TensorFlow",
      "Vue",
      "Flask",
      "Angular"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Vue"
  },
  {
    "skill": "React Native",
    "question": "Under which license is React Native primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "Apache‑2.0",
      "Public Domain",
      "MPL‑2.0",
      "MIT"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Which category best describes Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Mobile framework",
      "Programming language",
      "Technology",
      "Networking protocol"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Mobile framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Who primarily maintains Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Various",
      "Foundation",
      "Independent",
      "Community"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Various"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "In which year was Flutter first released?",
    "options": [
      "2006",
      "2011",
      "2008",
      "2005"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "What is a common file extension associated with Flutter?",
    "options": [
      ".ts",
      ".css",
      ".yaml",
      NaN
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "What is a primary use case of Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Working with mobile framework",
      "Working with messaging system",
      "Working with styling language",
      "Working with back‑end runtime"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Working with mobile framework"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Which command is commonly used to install or initialize Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "apt-get install pkg",
      NaN,
      "npm install package",
      "brew install pkg"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "What is the primary programming language associated with Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Rust",
      "Kotlin",
      NaN,
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "correct_answer": NaN
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Which of these is a key feature of Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Data manipulation",
      "Native bridges",
      "Strong typing",
      "Scalable compute"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Native bridges"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Which of the following could be considered a competitor or alternative to Flutter?",
    "options": [
      "Terraform",
      "GraphQL",
      "Jest",
      "React"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Terraform"
  },
  {
    "skill": "Flutter",
    "question": "Under which license is Flutter primarily distributed?",
    "options": [
      "MIT",
      "Public Domain",
      "GPL‑2.0",
      "MPL‑2.0"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Public Domain"
  }
]